bumrungrad.com 2011-03-23

# Bumrungrad International Hospital,Thailand - Privacy Policy

|  |  | 

[ Home](http://www.bumrungrad.com/overseas-medical-care/bumrungrad-international.aspx) > Privacy Policy   
  
---  
  
| 

##  The term "Bumrungrad Web" covers www.bumrungrad.com, www.plasticsurgerythailand.com, and www.e-vitallife.com (each a "website" and, collectively, the "Bumrungrad Web").

This privacy policy applies to Bumrungrad Web only and does not cover information collected on any third-party sites to which this Bumrungrad Weblinks. This policy covers information collected in conjunction with the use of Bumrungrad Web; it does not apply to patient medical records (which have their own, stricter privacy and confidentiality policies).

This privacy policy is part of, and must be read in conjunction with, Bumrungrad Web's Terms of Use. You can read the entire Terms of Use by clicking here or the menu at the bottom of every page of Bumrungrad Web. If you do not agree with the Terms of Use in their entirety, do not proceed any further.  
  
---  
   
Purpose of the Privacy Statement:   
Bumrungrad Web respects the privacy of visitors to this Bumrungrad Web and understands that information about you, your health, and your health care is sensitive. Bumrungrad Web will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information.

We encourage you to read this Internet Privacy Statement before using this Bumrungrad Web or submitting information. By using Bumrungrad Web, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to the terms of the Internet Privacy Statement.   

Information Voluntarily Provided by Users:  
  
You can visit much of Bumrungrad Web without telling us who you are or providing us with other personally identifiable information. Some areas of the Bumrungrad Web allow you to contact us to ask questions or provide comments. When you communicate with us and request a response, we ask for your name and contact information. We use this information so that we can respond more efficiently and keep track of our correspondence.

When you request an appointment we will ask for additional information. Our purpose is to begin identifying your medical and timing needs so that we can propose or schedule the appropriate services for you. This also helps us begin setting up a record for you, so that registration is easier when you arrive at the hospital. Finally, by requesting some basic information we discourage correspondence from those who are not serious about their healthcare, or might be contacting us for the wrong reasons. This allows us to focus more attention on patients who genuinely seek our help.  

Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information That You Provide Voluntarily:   
  
If you do provide us with personally identifiable information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, you agree that we may contact you through a variety of means such as postal mail, phone, or e-mail to provide you with information we believe may be of interest to you, unless you opt out of this service by contacting us as indicated below.

Except as provided in the Transfer of Control section, Bumrungrad Web will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information  

Use and Disclosure of Non-Personally Identifiable Information:  
  
Bumrungrad Web will not treat as confidential any information that you provide that is not personally identifiable, such as questions, comments, ideas, or suggestions. You should be aware that Bumrungrad Web will be free to disclose through any means and use for any purpose such information in its sole discretion.

By providing such information to Bumrungrad Web, you understand and agree that no relationship has been created between Bumrungrad Web and you, and Bumrungrad Web has no obligation to you whatsoever regarding that information.  

Update and Correction of Personally Identifiable Information:  
You may contact us to update or correct much of your personally identifiable information that you provide to us through the Bumrungrad Web, or to opt-out from our mailings and other services that you may have signed up for.   
   
Security:  
We take reasonable precautions to maintain the protection of personally identifiable information collected through this Bumrungrad Web and used in accordance with this Privacy Statement. In addition to technical safeguards, we also use physical controls and procedures to safeguard your personally identifiable information. However, we cannot guarantee that it is completely secure from people who might attempt to evade our security measures or intercept transmissions over the Internet.   
   
Use of Cookies:  
We may store some information on your computer using a technique your browser supports called "cookies". The cookies are used for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to helping you login (e.g., remembering your user name if you register or login), remembering some of your customized user preferences, to help us better understand how people use our Web site, and to help us improve our Web site. The cookies set by our Web sites are used only by our Web sites. To disable or limit the use of cookies, please refer to the options provided by your Internet browser. If you do so, however, some pages on this Bumrungrad Web may not work properly.   
   
Web Server Logging and IP Addresses:   
With or without cookies, our Bumrungrad Web keeps track of usage data, such as the source address that a page request is coming from (i.e., your IP address, domain name), date and time of the page request, the referring Bumrungrad Web (if any), and other parameters in the URL (e.g., search criteria). We use this data to better understand Bumrungrad Web usage on the whole and to determine which areas of our Bumrungrad Web users prefer (e.g., based on the number of visits to those areas). This information is stored in log files and is used by Bumrungrad Web for statistical reporting.   
   
Transfer of Control:   
Circumstances may arise where we decide to reorganize or divest part or all of our business or of a line of our business, including our information databases and Web sites, through a sale, divestiture, merger, acquisition, or other means of transfer. In any such circumstance, personally identifiable information may be shared with, sold, transferred, rented, licensed or otherwise provided or made available by us or on our behalf to actual or potential parties to, and in connection with, the contemplated transaction (without your consent or any further notice to you). In such circumstances, we will seek written assurances that personally identifiable information submitted through this Bumrungrad Web will be protected appropriately.  
   
Changes in Our Privacy Statement:   
Bumrungrad Web may at any time revise this privacy statement by updating this posting. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the most current privacy statement.  
   
Questions:   
If you have any questions about the Web site’s Internet Privacy Statement or other aspects of privacy on our Web site, please contact us via our [ feedback form](http://www.bumrungrad.com/overseas-medical-care/contact-us/feedback.aspx "Feedback").
